## Will

## Godwin

Web Developer

Phone: 0414 487 511

Email: willygodwin47@gmail.com

Perth, WA, Australia

LinkedIn

Github

% Portfolio

## PROFILE

Junior Web-Developer with a passion for creating interactive web environments.

Confident in front end and back-end development with experience in the design, installation, testing and maintenance of webapplications. Ability to acquire new skills fast and enjoy challenging myself.

Proficient in technologies such as react, Javascript, CSS, HTML, node.js, express.js, mongoDB and MySQL. Experience in C, Java and Python. Able to self-manage smaller projects or collaborate in a team environment.

## EDUCATION

#### Bachelor of Software Engineering

University of Western Australia Feb 2020 – Current

### Coding Bootcamp

University of Western Australia November 2020 – May 2021

# Bachelor of Applied Science (Construction Management)

Curtin University
Feb 2015 – November 2018

## PROJECTS

### Project 1 - Tombola

Tombola is a fun and exciting adaptation of the online marketplace. Sellers are able to raffle consumer items to the community. Buyers from the community then have a chance to win items by purchasing a percentage of these tickets.

## Project 2 - Jiffy

Developed full-stack application both front and back-end. I personally developed the landing page, dashboard and used passport.js for the signup and login features.

## Project 3 - Reci-bits

Developed the Auto-complete feature for the search bar, used AJAX and external API's to populate the Recipe Lists and Modal Pop Up, developed the Star Button to save to favourite recipes.

## EXPERIENCE

#### Barista

Kirkwood Deli August 2019-Current

#### Contracts Administrator

PS Structures January 2016-January 2019

Successfully managed the subcontractor budgets for the Bethanie on the Park Aged Development and the Armadale Aquatic Aquatic Centre and worked on pricing over 50+ tenders.